{
    "id": "fa6080cafe724462a57bc33218f390ce",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "……………….. working hard, he failed the test.",
            "description": "Despite is a preposition we use a preposition before an ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "Despite",
                "However",
                "Though"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ………………….. to beat his opponent.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too strong",
                "enough strong",
                "strong enough"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………… the thief saw the cops coming, he ran away.",
            "description": "As soon as is used to say that something happens immediately after something else has happened. ",
            "answers": [
                "As soon as",
                "No sooner",
                "Scarcely"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………… he is so ill, the doctors do not expect him to recover.",
            "description": "As gives the reason.",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Though",
                "If"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy ………………….. watch had been stolen complained to the teacher.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whose",
                "who's"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. on tip-toe, he reached for the apple.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Standing",
                "Stood",
                "Having standing"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He will ………………….. spend his money nor invest it.",
            "description": "Note the pattern neither/nor.",
            "answers": [
                "neither",
                "either",
                "both"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the hotel …………………… our meetings usually take place.",
            "description": "Where indicates position.",
            "answers": [
                "where",
                "there",
                "whence"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I prefer reading books …………………… watching TV.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "than",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The house is …………………….. to accommodate all.",
            "description": "When enough is an adverb, it goes after the adjective or adverb modified by it. ",
            "answers": [
                "so spacious",
                "too spacious",
                "spacious enough"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The germ is ……………………. small to be seen with the naked eye.",
            "description": "Note the pattern too..to..",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "so",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………. had the hunter raised the gun, than the birds flew away.",
            "description": "We need a comparative expression before than.",
            "answers": [
                "No sooner",
                "As soon as",
                "Hardly"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}